Going viral is a nightmare.
Dear David is a horror, thriller film directed by John McPhail.
Shortly after comic artist Adam responds to Internet
trolls, he begins experiencing sleep paralysis.
As he chronicles increasingly malevolent occurrences in a series of tweets, Adam begins
to believe he is being haunted by the ghost of a dead child named David.
Adam Ellis, played by Augustus Prew.
Linda, played by Rachel Wilson.
Bryce, played by Justin Long.
Evelyn, played by Andrea Bang.
Kyle Sanchez, played by René Escobar Jr..
Dear David, played by Cameron Nicoll.
Dear David is a 2023 American supernatural horror film directed by John
McPhail, based on Adam Ellis's Twitter thread of the same name.
It stars Augustus Prew, with Andrea Bang, René Escobar Jr.,
Cameron Nicoll, and Justin Long in supporting roles.
Produced by BuzzFeed Studios, the film follows BuzzFeed employee Ellis (Prew), as his attempt to
retaliate against online trolls results in a haunting from a demon-possessed spirit.
Dear David was released in theaters and to streaming and digital formats on
October 13, 2023, by Lionsgate Films, to negative reviews from critics.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and intense.